Marvin Leath papers, Inclusive: 1954-1994, undated; Bulk: 1979-1991
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1978-1991, undated; 6
  - Bills, 1979-1990; 3
    - 100th Congress, 1987-1988; 5
      - H.R. 3228, Superconducting Super Collider Program Appropriations, 1987 (Box 377, Folder 31)
      - H.R. 3338, Deny Most-Favored-Nation Treatment to Iranian Products, 1987 (Box 377, Folder 32)
      - H.R. 3400, Federal Employees Political Activities Act, 1987 (Box 377, Folder 33)
      - H.R. 3454, Medicaid Home & Community Quality Services Act, 1987 (Box 377, Folder 34)
      - H.R. 3509, Relief of Henry Johnson, 1987 (Box 377, Folder 35)
      - H.R. 3627, Prohibit United Soviet Social Republics (USSR) Trade with Afghanistan, 1987 (Box 377, Folder 36)
      - H.R. 3723, Protect Rural Electrification Administration Loan Guarantee Programs from Interagency Disputes, 1987 (Box 377, Folder 37)
      - H.R. 3791, Federal Retiree Prompt Pay Act, 1987 (Box 377, Folder 38)
      - H.R. 3907, Repeal Unfair Accounting Burden on Farmers, 1988 (Box 377, Folder 39)
      - H.R. 4000, Tax-Free Diesel Fuel for State & Local Governments, 1988 (Box 377, Folder 40)
      - H.R. 4011, Farm & Firefighting Vehicles Exempt from Commercial Vehicle Operation Requirements, 1988 (Box 377, Folder 41)
      - H.R. 4074, Use of American Airports on a Cost-Recovery Basis, 1988 (Box 377, Folder 42)
      - H.R. 4127, American Heritage Trust Act, 1988 (Box 377, Folder 43)
      - H.R. 4128, Defense Industrial Base Preservation Act, 1988 (Box 377, Folder 44)
      - H.R. 4150, Postal Reorganization Act Amendments, 1988 (Box 377, Folder 45)
      - H.R. 4155, “Dan Daniel Armed Forces Recreation Center”, 1988 (Box 377, Folder 46)
      - H.R. 4192, Tax-Free Diesel Fuel Purchases Under Revised Diesel Fuel Tax, 1988 (Box 377, Folder 47)
      - H.R. 4213, Montgomery GI Bill Amendments, 1988 (Box 377, Folder 48)
      - H.R. 4230, Omnibus Antidrug Abuse Act, 1988 (Box 377, Folder 49)
      - H.R. 4257, Prevent Mailing of Unsolicited Sexually Oriented Advertisements, 1988 (Box 377, Folder 50)
      - H.R. 4258, Apply the H-2A Temporary Agricultural Worker Program to Agricultural Labor & Services, 1988 (Box 377, Folder 51)
      - H.R. 4279, Transportation Regulations on Overseas United States Military Installations, 1988 (Box 377, Folder 52)
      - H.R. 4446, Provide for a Drug-Free America, 1988 (Box 378, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 4542, Asset Sales by Cooperatives, 1988 (Box 378, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 4606, United States-Mexico Border Regional Development Act, 1988 (Box 378, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 4678, Extend Low-Income Housing Credit Through 1990, 1988 (Box 378, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 4741, Veterans Compensation Amendments, 1988 (Box 378, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 4681, Grant Appropriations for State Veterans Cemeteries, 1988 (Box 378, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 4924, In-Flight Emergency Medical Assistance Act, 1988 (Box 378, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 4926, Establish the Amistad National Recreation Area, 1988 (Box 378, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 5019, Federal Communications Commission Protection of Small Telephone Company Subscribers, 1988 (Box 378, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 5151, No Long-Term Contract If Construction is Completed Within a Twelve-Month Period, 1988 (Box 378, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 5221, Veterans Home Loan Mortgage Indemnity Act, 1988 (Box 378, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 5410, Foreign Ownership Disclosure Act, 1988 (Box 378, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 5479, Older Women’s Cancer Prevention Act, 1988 (Box 378, Folder 13)
    - 101st Congress, 1989-1990; 6
      - H.R. 3, Essential Air Service Program, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 5, Foreign Ownership Disclosure Act, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 15)
      - H. J. R. 8, Establish a Joint Committee on Intelligence, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 18, Prohibit Omnibus Long-Term Continuing Resolutions, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 20, Establish a Select Committee on Hunger, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 18)
      - H.R. 20, Federal Employees Political Activities Act, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 19)
      - H.R. 23, Establish the Select Committee on Narcotics Abuse & Control, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 20)
      - H. Con. Res. 26, Stop Unfair Assault on U.S. Meat Exports, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 21)
      - H. Con. Res. 34, Formulation of a National Energy Policy, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 22)
      - H. Con. Res. 37, Keep Current Federal Income Tax Deduction for Interest Paid on Debt, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 23)
      - H. Con. Res. 39, Tax Exempt Bonds, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 24)
      - H. Con. Res. 40, Protect Medicare 90 Concurrent Resolution, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 25)
      - H.R. 41, No Increase in Federal Excise Taxes on Gas & Diesel, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 26)
      - H.R. 60, Repeal Estate Freeze Rules, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 27)
      - H.J.R. 80, Stop Unfair Trade Practices Against Equitable & Hard-Won Export Markets, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 28)
      - H. Con. Res. 83, Medicare Physician Reimbursement Reform, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 29)
      - H.R. 88, Arlington Cemetery Unmarked Burial Act, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 30)
      - H.R. 98, Guam Commonwealth Act, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 31)
      - H. Con. Res. 119, Honoring the Texas-Israel Exchange Program, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 32)
      - H.R. 125, Eliminate the Medicare Urban-Rural Differential, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 33)
      - H.R. 134, No Increase of Federal Excise Tax Rates, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 34)
      - H.R. 137, Congressional Metal License Tags, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 35)
      - H.R. 172, Truth in Legislating Resolution, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 36)
      - H. Con. Res. 183, Extradition of Sheik Abdul Obeid, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 37)
      - H.R. 184, Protect American Flag from Desecration, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 38)
      - H.R. 185, Constitution Permits Prohibition on American Flag Desecration, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 39)
      - H.R. 189, “Take Pride in the Flag Day”, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 40)
      - H. Con. Res. 194, Congressional Support for the Colombian People, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 41)
      - H.R. 214, Restore Tax Fairness for Federal Employees, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 42)
      - H.R. 215, Federal Employee Irregular Overtime Premium Pay, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 43)
      - H.R. 239, First Time Home Buyer’s Act, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 44)
      - H. Con. Res. 252, Congressional Policy on Cost-of-Living Adjustment for Civil Service Retirees, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 45)
      - H. Con. Res. 267, Felony Charge for Demonstrators Who Threw Blood on United States Capitol & White House, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 46)
      - H.J.R. 268, Balanced Budget Amendment, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 47)
      - H.R. 286, Infrastructure Protection Act, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 48)
      - H.J.R. 302, Congressional & State Prohibition of American Flag Desecration, 1989 (Box 378, Folder 49)
      - H.J.R. 305, Constitutional Amendment Prohibiting American Flag Desecration, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 1)
      - H.J.R. 308, Constitutional Amendment Prohibiting American Flag Desecration, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 2)
      - H.J.R. 309, Constitutional Amendment Prohibiting American Flag Desecration, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 3)
      - H.J.R. 317, Constitutional Amendment Prohibiting American Flag Desecration, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 4)
      - H.J.R. 318, Constitutional Amendment Prohibiting American Flag Desecration, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 5)
      - H.J.R. 321, Balanced Budget Amendment, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 6)
      - H.J.R. 324, Constitutional Amendment Prohibiting American Flag Desecration, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 7)
      - H.J.R. 330, Constitutional Amendment Prohibiting American Flag Desecration, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 8)
      - H.J.R. 337, Constitutional Amendment Prohibiting American Flag Desecration, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 9)
      - H.J.R. 350, Constitutional Amendment Prohibiting American Flag Desecration, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 371, Study of Anhydrous Ammonia as a Poisonous Gas, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 11)
      - H.J.R. 401, “Country Music Month”, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 402, Designate Two House of Representatives Office Buildings, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 421, Continue Six-Day Postal Service & One Day First Class Service, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 14)
      - H.J.R. 492, “National Doctor’s Day”, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 15)
      - H.R. 505, Circulation Coin Modernization, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 515, “National Give Kids a Fighting Chance Week”, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 518, “American Textile Industry Bicentennial Week”, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 18)
      - H.R. 519, “National Sarcoidosis Awareness Day”, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 19)
      - H.R. 537, Established a World War II Memorial & Museum, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 20)
      - H.J.R. 546, “Infant Mortality Awareness Day”, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 21)
      - H.J.R. 554, “National Law Enforcement Training Week”, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 22)
      - H.J.R. 559, Constitutional Amendment Prohibiting American Flag Desecration, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 23)
      - H.J.R. 566, “National Military Families Recognition Day”, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 24)
      - H.J.R. 595, “National Red Ribbon Week for a Drug-Free America”, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 25)
      - H.J.R. 596, “Rose Fitzgerald Kennedy Family Appreciation Day”, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 26)
      - H.J.R. 606, “Lithuanian Independence Day”, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 27)
      - H.R. 634, Repeal Non-Discrimination Rules of IRS Code Section 89, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 28)
      - H.J.R. 637, “National Rice Month”, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 29)
      - H.J.R. 640, “Year of Thanksgiving for the Blessings of Liberty”, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 30)
      - H.R. 642, Pickle “Cash Loss” Bill, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 31)
      - H.R. 659, Energy Security Tax Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 32)
      - H.J.R. 667, “National Federation of the Blind Day”, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 33)
      - H.J.R. 669, Congratulate Poland on 200th Anniversary of the Polish Constitution, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 34)
      - H.J.R. 673, National Day of Prayer for American Military Forces, 1990 (Box 379, Folder 35)
      - H.R. 676, In-Flight Emergency Medical Assistance Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 36)
      - H.R. 694, Self-Employed Individual Health Insurance Deduction, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 37)
      - H.R. 746, National Observance Advisory Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 38)
      - H.R. 760, Energy Tax Reform Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 39)
      - H.R. 762, Equity for Rural Hospitals Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 40)
      - H.R. 764, Reserve Acreage Water Storage, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 41)
      - H.R. 772, Great Plains Conservation Program Extension, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 42)
      - H.R. 901, Veterans Health-Care Programs Amendments, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 43)
      - H.R. 953, Establish the Position of Assistant Secretary for Natural Gas, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 44)
      - H.R. 971, Telephone Operator Consumer Protection Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 45)
      - H.R. 982, Postal Reorganization Act Amendments, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 46)
      - H.R. 1059, Federal Retirees Fairness Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 47)
      - H.R. 1083, Expand Civil Service Retirement Provisions, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 48)
      - H.R. 1157, Relief of Henry Johnson, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 49)
      - H.R. 1158, Relief of Doris Miller, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 50)
      - H.R. 1197, Federal Law Enforcement Officers Death Penalty Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 51)
      - H.R. 1210, Pornographic Mail Prohibition Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 52)
      - H.R. 1227, Limitation on State Taxation of Pension Income, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 53)
      - H.R. 1287, Repeal of Certain Limitations on One-Time Exclusion of Gain from Sale of Principal Residence, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 54)
      - H.R. 1295, Forbid Display of American Flag on Floor or Ground, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 55)
      - H.R. 1296, Prohibit Imposition of “User Fees” for Military Outpatient Care, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 56)
      - H.R. 1307, General Aviation Standards Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 57)
      - H.R. 1334, Remove Pension Limitation on Long-Term Veterans Hospital Care, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 58)
      - H.R. 1400, Extend Federal Civil Service Credit for Certain National Guard Technicians, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 59)
      - H.R. 1416, Research & Experimental Credit Extension & Reform Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 60)
      - H.R. 1451, Terrorist Alien Removal Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 61)
      - H.R. 1515, Anti-Terrorism Sanctions Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 62)
      - H.R. 1583, Rural Hospital Recovery Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 63)
      - H.R. 1586, Study of Medicare Reimbursement for Ambulance Services, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 64)
      - H.R. 1652, Recycling Information Clearinghouse Act, 1989 (Box 379, Folder 65)
      - H.R. 1679, United States-Mexico Border Regional Development Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 1692, Medical Care Quality Research & Improvement Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 2023, Organ Transportation Good Samaritan Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 2121, Extend & Increase Health Insurance Deduction Cost for Self-Employed Individuals, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 2259, Davis-Bacon Reform Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 2269, Alternative Fuels Incentive Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 2273, Americans with Disabilities Act (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 380, Folder 7)
      - 8H.R. 2273, Americans with Disabilities Act (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 380, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 2334, Homer Thornberry Judicial Building, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 2353, Tax Treatment of Farming Cooperatives Asset Sales, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 2388, Rural Housing Improvement Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 2486, Veterans Recruitment Authority Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 2569, Aleda E. Lutz Department of Veterans Affairs Medical Center, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 2712, Emergency Chinese Adjustment of Status Facilitation Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 15)
      - H.R. 2761, United Services Organization’s 50th Anniversary Commemorative Coin Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 2884, Legal Services Administration Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 2972, Drug War Bond Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 18)
      - H.R. 3001, Hostages Released Before Reparations to Iranians, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 19)
      - H.R. 3017, Industrial Design Anti-Piracy Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 20)
      - H.R. 3030, Clean Air Act Amendments, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 21)
      - H.R. 3051, Revoke Driver’s Licenses of Illegal Drug Users, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 22)
      - H.R. 3056, Benjamin Franklin National Memorial Commemorative Coin Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 23)
      - H.R. 3139, Portability of Benefits for Department of Defense Non-Appropriated Fund Employees Act of 1989 (Box 380, Folder 24)
      - H.R. 3238, Death Penalty for Drug Traffickers, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 25)
      - H.R. 3252, Establish the Margaret Walker Alexander National African-American Research Center, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 26)
      - H.R. 3270, Farm Animal & Research Facilities Protection Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 27)
      - H.R. 3274, Establish the Essential Air Service Program, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 28)
      - H.R. 3318, Mickey Leland Federal Building, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 29)
      - H.R. 3382, Rural Business & Job Creation Grants, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 30)
      - H.R. 3429, Interstate Greyhound Racing Act of 1990, 1989-1990 (Box 380, Folder 31)
      - H.R. 3484, Consumer Awareness & Trademark Protection Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 32)
      - H.R. 3500, Small Business Access Improvement Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 33)
      - H.R. 3735, Waste Materials Management Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 34)
      - H.R. 3800, Expedited Consideration of Proposed Rescissions Act, 1989 (Box 380, Folder 35)
      - H.R. 4062, Emergency Federal Judgeship Act, 1990 (Box 380, Folder 36)
      - H.R. 4087, Veterans Employment & Training Amendments, 1990 (Box 380, Folder 37)
      - H.R. 4098, Benjamin Franklin National Memorial Commemorative Coin Act, 1990 (Box 380, Folder 38)
      - H.R. 4181, Medicaid State Share Protection Amendments, 1990 (Box 380, Folder 39)
      - H.R. 4336, Organ Procurement Process Review Act, 1990 (Box 380, Folder 40)
      - H.R. 4341, Medical School Research Center Grants, 1990 (Box 380, Folder 41)
      - H.R. 4365, World War II 50th Anniversary Commemorative Coin Act, 1990 (Box 380, Folder 42)
      - H.R. 4390, Medical School Research Center Grants for Veterans Affairs Medical Research, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 4430, Military Homeowners Assistance Program, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 4475, Medicare Physician Regulation Relief Amendments, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 4487, National Health Service Corps Revitalization Amendments, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 4494, Limit Foreclosure & Estate Liabilities, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 4495, Peer Review Organization Investigation of Hospital Dumping Violation, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 4496, Textile, Apparel, & Footwear Trade Act, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 4690, Loan Deferments for Students, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 4892, Disaster Assistance Act, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 4962, 1992 Olympic Commemorative Coin Act, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 5002, Veterans Housing & Homeless Amendments, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 5013, Pesticide Export Regulations, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 5053, Korean War Veterans Memorial 38th Anniversary Commemorative Coin Act, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 5212, Ice Enforcement & Prevention Act, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 5453, Airline Passengers Defense Act, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 15)
      - H.R. 5633, Task Force on the Education of Federally-Connected Dependents, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 5652, Redefine American Legion Membership Eligibility, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 5739, Samuel S. Stratton Department of Veterans Affairs Medical Center, 1990 (Box 381, Folder 18)
- Press, 1979-1990, undated; 7
  This large and comprehensive series includes seven subseries: Audio Tape Transcripts, Newsletters, Newsletter Comments, Newsletter Drafts, Newspaper Clippings, Press Releases and Mailings, and Speeches and Radio Scripts from 1979-1990. Leath was famous for his well-written and insightful newsletters replete with catchy and clever titles. Also of interest is Leath’s endorsement speech of Chet Edwards (who succeeded Leath as the district’s representative). Audio tape transcripts are based on audio recordings of his newsletters (recordings are in the A/V series). The mailings subseries includes special mailings and postal patron mailings sent out by Leath. Moreover, the Newsletter Drafts subseries contains his handwritten drafts while the Newsletters section holds the final printed versions. Within the series, the first five and the seventh series are chronologically arranged by year but the sixth (Press Releases and Mailings) is alpha-ordered. In the Newsletter subseries, many duplicate files were deaccessioned. Radio scripts numbers 1-49 are missing in the subseries of the same name.
  - Audio Tape Transcripts, 1979-1980; 1
    - A Bushel of Wheat for a Barrel of Oil, 1979 May 10 (Box 381, Folder 19)
    - A Time of Decision, 1979 November 15 (Box 381, Folder 20)
    - And Now Gun Control, 1979 March 30 (Box 381, Folder 21)
    - Audio Transcript #1, 1979 March 14 (Box 381, Folder 22)
    - August Time Will Be Well Spent, 1979 August 10 (Box 381, Folder 23)
    - Bureaucrats and Firearms, 1979 October 18 (Box 381, Folder 24)
    - Energy, 1979 April 11 (Box 381, Folder 25)
    - Fuel for Our Defense Needs, 1979 (Box 381, Folder 26)
    - Guess Who Is Paying the Bill, 1979 November 6 (Box 381, Folder 27)
    - Here We Go Again, 1979 November 1 (Box 381, Folder 28)
    - Meet the Member, 1979 June 11 (Box 381, Folder 29)
    - Memo to Station Managers, 1979 January 17 (Box 381, Folder 30)
    - Middle East, What Is Our Best Interest, 1979 September 27 (Box 381, Folder 31)
    - New Funding for Social Security, 1979 June 28 (Box 381, Folder 32)
    - Now Is the Time, 1979 June 21 (Box 381, Folder 33)
    - One More Giant Step Backward, 1979 May 22 (Box 381, Folder 34)
    - Panama CanalDL Bad Deal Gets Worse, 1979 March 22 (Box 381, Folder 35)
    - Paper Dollar and Inflation, 1979 October 2 (Box 381, Folder 36)
    - Reflections on Energy, Part I, 1979 June 6 (Box 381, Folder 37)
    - Reflections on Energy, Part II, 1979 June 12 (Box 381, Folder 38)
    - Reflections on The First Year, 1979 December 20 (Box 381, Folder 39)
    - Stop the Waste Congressman-But!, 1979 September 13 (Box 381, Folder 40)
    - Strategic Arms Limitation Treaty (SALT) II, 1979 April 1 (Box 381, Folder 41)
    - Terrorism, 1979 December 5 (Box 381, Folder 42)
    - The China Syndrome-Fact or Fiction?, 1979 May 2 (Box 381, Folder 43)
    - The Federal Budget-Moving in the Right Direction, 1979 May 17 (Box 381, Folder 44)
    - The Free Market, 1979 August 1 (Box 381, Folder 45)
    - The Middle East- An Overall View, 1979 November 28 (Box 381, Folder 46)
    - The President on National Defense, 1979 December 14 (Box 381, Folder 47)
    - The President’s Energy Message, 1979 July 19 (Box 381, Folder 48)
    - The System, 1979 May 30 (Box 381, Folder 49)
    - The Tip of The Iceberg, 1979 September 20 (Box 381, Folder 50)
    - The Ultimate Special Interest, 1979 November 20 (Box 381, Folder 51)
    - Trade Bill- A Plus for Texas, 1979 July 12 (Box 381, Folder 52)
    - US Generous to A Fault, 1979 October 11 (Box 381, Folder 53)
    - We Should Look to The Experts, 1979 July 25 (Box 381, Folder 54)
    - What Are You Doing About It Congressman, 1979 October 25 (Box 381, Folder 55)
    - Who Does Your Government Represent?, 1979 April 26 (Box 381, Folder 56)
    - #6, 1979 April 11 (Box 381, Folder 57)
    - A Time for Truth; A Time For Unity, 1980 February 7 (Box 381, Folder 58)
    - Interest Rates and the Economy, 1980 February 21 (Box 381, Folder 59)
    - More Waste Revealed, 1980 June 26 (Box 381, Folder 60)
    - Refugees, 1980 May 22 (Box 381, Folder 61)
    - Summer Travels, 1980 June 19 (Box 381, Folder 62)
    - The 11th District of Texas, 1980 June 5 (Box 381, Folder 63)
    - The 1981 Budget, 1980 May 13 (Box 381, Folder 64)
    - The Draft, 1980 February 18 (Box 381, Folder 65)
    - The Economy, 1980 May 8 (Box 381, Folder 66)
    - The Legislative Process, 1980 June 12 (Box 381, Folder 67)
    - Where the Rubber Meets the Road, 1980 May 29 (Box 381, Folder 68)
  - Newsletters, 1979-1990; 2
    - A Bushel of Wheat for A Barrel of Oil, 1979 May 11 (Box 382, Folder 1)
    - An Amendment to Balance the Budget, 1979 February 16 (Box 382, Folder 2)
    - And Now Gun Control?, 1979 March 30 (Box 382, Folder 3)
    - August-Time Will Be Well Spent, 1979 August 10 (Box 382, Folder 4)
    - Bureaucrats and Firearms, 1979 October 19 (Box 382, Folder 5)
    - Cuts in the Fiscal Year ’79 Budget and Spending Priorities, 1979 March 9 (Box 382, Folder 6)
    - Energy- A Step in the Right Direction, 1979 April 13 (Box 382, Folder 7)
    - Examining America’s ConscienceEL, 1979 March 16 (Box 382, Folder 8)
    - Fuel for Our Defense Needs, 1979 June 29 (Box 382, Folder 9)
    - Guess Who Is Paying the Bill?, 1979 November 9 (Box 382, Folder 10)
    - Here We Go Again!, 1979 November 2 (Box 382, Folder 11)
    - Insuring A Water Supply, 1979 April 20 (Box 382, Folder 12)
    - IranDLA Time of Decision, 1979 November 16 (Box 382, Folder 13)
    - Middle EastDLWhat Is Our Best Interest?, 1979 September 27 (Box 382, Folder 14)
    - More Opportunities for Service, 1979 February 23 (Box 382, Folder 15)
    - Movers and Farmers, 1979 February 9 (Box 382, Folder 16)